[
  {
    "counter":1,
    "center":[
      53.348765,
      -6.261174
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Dublin",
    "wrong":[
      "Wien",
      "Athen",
      "Prag"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":2,
    "center":[
      59.437597,
      24.745399
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Tallin",
    "wrong":[
      "Brüssel",
      "Madrid",
      "Sofia"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":3,
    "center":[
      56.947708,
      24.107852
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Riga",
    "wrong":[
      "Vilnius",
      "Lissabon",
      "Madrid"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":4,
    "center":[
      37.976401,
      23.726125
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Athen",
    "wrong":[
      "Madrid",
      "Ljubljana",
      "Tallin"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":5,
    "center":[
      48.206024,
      16.369855
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Wien",
    "wrong":[
      "Warschau",
      "Vilnius",
      "Helsinki"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":6,
    "center":[
      47.491044,
      19.05042
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Budapest",
    "wrong":[
      "Helsinki",
      "Amsterdam",
      "Stockholm"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":7,
    "center":[
      40.416846,
      -3.703761
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Madrid",
    "wrong":[
      "Tallin",
      "Bratislava",
      "Vilnius"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":8,
    "center":[
      52.371619,
      4.901036
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Amsterdam",
    "wrong":[
      "Tallin",
      "Wien",
      "Madrid"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":9,
    "center":[
      55.677035,
      12.585253
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Kopenhagen",
    "wrong":[
      "Luxemburg",
      "Paris",
      "Zagreb"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":10,
    "center":[
      60.167603,
      24.942042
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Helsinki",
    "wrong":[
      "Riga",
      "Madrid",
      "Berlin"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":11,
    "center":[
      35.170792,
      33.363981
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Nicosia",
    "wrong":[
      "Zagreb",
      "Amsterdam",
      "Vilnius"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":12,
    "center":[
      59.325111,
      18.071141
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Stockholm",
    "wrong":[
      "Nicosia",
      "Vilnius",
      "Bratislava"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":13,
    "center":[
      49.611969,
      6.131068
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Luxemburg",
    "wrong":[
      "Brüssel",
      "Bratislava",
      "Budapest"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":14,
    "center":[
      42.696847,
      23.321052
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Sofia",
    "wrong":[
      "Helsinki",
      "Tallin",
      "Amsterdam"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":15,
    "center":[
      35.898354,
      14.512695
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Valetta",
    "wrong":[
      "Bratislava",
      "Kopenhagen",
      "Bukarest"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":16,
    "center":[
      48.853941,
      2.347694
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Paris",
    "wrong":[
      "Amsterdam",
      "Warschau",
      "Ljubljana"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":17,
    "center":[
      48.148888,
      17.109876
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Bratislava",
    "wrong":[
      "Brüssel",
      "Sofia",
      "Valetta"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":18,
    "center":[
      41.892648,
      12.485901
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Rom",
    "wrong":[
      "Ljubljana",
      "Vilnius",
      "Zagreb"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":19,
    "center":[
      38.709313,
      -9.13734
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Lissabon",
    "wrong":[
      "Sofia",
      "Madrid",
      "Riga"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":20,
    "center":[
      45.812855,
      15.978194
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Zagreb",
    "wrong":[
      "Paris",
      "Sofia",
      "Ljubljana"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":21,
    "center":[
      46.050108,
      14.50683
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Ljubljana",
    "wrong":[
      "Helsinki",
      "Lissabon",
      "Bratislava"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":22,
    "center":[
      54.682097,
      25.286986
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Vilnius",
    "wrong":[
      "Sofia",
      "Riga",
      "Stockholm"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":23,
    "center":[
      50.086405,
      14.412716
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Prag",
    "wrong":[
      "Bukarest",
      "Dublin",
      "Nicosia"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":24,
    "center":[
      52.517415,
      13.393369
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Berlin",
    "wrong":[
      "Budapest",
      "Brüssel",
      "Wien"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":25,
    "center":[
      44.431263,
      26.101768
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Bukarest",
    "wrong":[
      "Luxemburg",
      "Lissabon",
      "Nicosia"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":26,
    "center":[
      52.232488,
      21.014303
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Warschau",
    "wrong":[
      "Bukarest",
      "Paris",
      "Nicosia"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  },
  {
    "counter":27,
    "center":[
      50.847571,
      4.352293
    ],
    "zoomlevel":15,
    "correct":"Brüssel",
    "wrong":[
      "Bukarest",
      "Ljubljana",
      "Zagreb"
    ],
    "question":"Welche Stadt sieht man hier?"
  }
]